The greatest adventure history has ever revealed.
National Treasure: Book of Secrets is a action, adventure,
mystery film directed by Jon Turteltaub.
Benjamin Franklin Gates and Abigail Chase re-team with Riley Poole and, now armed with a stack of long-lost pages from John Wilkes
Booth's diary, Ben must follow a clue left there to prove his ancestor's innocence in the assassination of Abraham Lincoln.
Benjamin Franklin Gates, played by Nicolas Cage.
Abigail Chase, played by Diane Kruger.
Riley Poole, played by Justin Bartha.
Mitch Wilkinson, played by Ed Harris.
Patrick Gates, played by Jon Voight.
Emily Appleton, played by Helen Mirren.
National Treasure: Book of Secrets is a 2007 American action-adventure film
directed by Jon Turteltaub and produced by Jerry Bruckheimer.
It is a sequel to the 2004 film National Treasure and is the
second film of the National Treasure franchise.
The film stars Nicolas Cage in the lead role, Jon Voight, Harvey Keitel, Ed
Harris, Diane Kruger, Justin Bartha, Bruce Greenwood and Helen Mirren.
The film premiered in New York City on December 13, 2007, and Walt Disney
Studios Motion Pictures released it in North America on December 21.
Like its predecessor, it received mixed reviews from critics but was a commercial success,
grossing $459 million worldwide, becoming the ninth-highest-grossing film of 2007.
The film explores themes of gold, treasure, london,
england, assassination, usa president.
The tone is intense and mind_bending.